[person gasping]
[gasping continues]
[gasping]
[excited laughter. chatter]
[♪ eerie music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[chatter continues]
[woman] Look. there's a kitty cat.
Come on.
-Okay. what do you say?
-Trick or treat.
Oh. you look so cute.
Let me just go get something.
I have great big candy bars inside.
[groaning]
[door closes]
Where is it?
Mm.
♪
Ah! In here. yes!
Where are you goin'?
[panting]
I'll be back in a minute.
Sorry. I don't have candy bars.
But you can have these.
We can only accept wrapped candy.
So sorry.
That's really smart.
Your mom takes really good care of you.
Stay safe out there.
[person grunting]
Hm.
What are you doin'?
Well that was stupid.
[mask dropping]
[weakly] Please.
[footsteps thumping]
[gasping]
[shushing]
Shh!
It's probably time. right?
[gasping]
[gasping deeply]
[wheezing exhale]
[raspy inhale]
[whispers]
I don't really like listening to you.
[raspy exhale]
I don't like the sounds you're making.
[raspy breath]
But I love your smile.
It's like...
[inhales]
[candy clinking]
♪
[phone ringing]
Hi. I'm Agent Alice Black.
How can I help you?
[caller 1] You're not from the FBI.
You're lying to me.
I am a real FBI agent.
Then why are you on the phone?
Yes. I'm Agent Alice Black
at FBI New York.
Is there something you'd like to report?
[caller 2] Lick my butt!
I'm not gonna be able to do that for you
at this time. but thank you for calling.
I'm new here.
I'm a duty agent.
Is there something you'd like to report?
[caller 3] Duty agent?
I want to talk to someone higher up.
There's no one else available.
You're stuck with me.
Hi. I'm Agent Alice Black.
Is there something you'd like to report?
[caller 4]
You sound so smart and pretty.
-Thank you.
-Are you married?
My son is single.
and he's a real catch.
-Mets or Yankees?
-Oh. Mets.
-Deal breaker?
-Oh. he'll love you.
[agent] [softly] It's her.
Come on. come on. come on.
[caller 5] The White House
is hacking all of my machines.
-All of my internet.
-All of your internet?
-That's bad.
-Yes!
-Can you help me?
-So. you're gonna want to cover
everything you have in tinfoil.
-And then you're...
-What line is she on?
-She called five times last...
-What line?
Two.
Hi. I'm Agent Alice Black.
How can I...
Excuse me. what was he saying
about the tinfoil?
Don't worry about that.
Just tell me everything that's happened.
and take your time.
[sighs]
-[headset clattering]
-[exhales sharply]
[message chiming]
[knocking]
You wanted to see me?
You need to stay in your lane.
Why am I being told
a Brooklyn homicide detective
wants your advice
on an overdose death?
I worked out of the Brooklyn North
Homicide Squad when I was with the NYPD.
I don't care what you did at the NYPD.
Your job now is to stay
in the applicant pool
and answer the phone
when the crazy people Google the FBI
and call the number on the bottom
of their screen.
I know you requested
to be assigned to sex crimes.
but leadership will assign you
an operational squad when you're ready.
-I know that.
-You know a detective named. uh...
-[computer mouse clicking]
-Danny Kelly?
-'Cause he requested your help.
-I do.
We worked homicide
at Brooklyn North together.
Is this the officer you disclosed
having a domestic relationship with?
That wasn't him.
That was someone else.
What happened?
Bad breakup. so you came
running over here?
'Cause I like to know
these things in advance.
Yeah. and I just told you.
What would you like me to do?
Catch up on the information they sent.
drive to the crime scene. write it up.
and then come back here
and do your actual job.
[clicking tongue] Oh. and. uh.
stop at Costco on your way back.
It's your day for snacks.
Oh. we got the fucking FBI here.
What are you doing?
You quit.
Not on weekdays.
I only smoke on weekdays now.
Oh yeah?
That'll fucking work.
Why am I here?
I'm busy.
Sitting around
doing background checks?
No.
-Doesn't that hurt?
-Yeah.
I don't know why the fuck
I just did that.
Come on. What is this?
What do you want from me?
What do I want from you?
If you wanted to talk to me.
you could have just faked a heart attack.
-No. you wouldn't have come.
-[clicking tongue] You're right.
I would've sent flowers.
[chuckles]
You wouldn't have fucking sent flowers.
My divorce is final.
Yesterday.
-Yesterday?
-Mm-hmm.
Wow. you came back.
I'm not back.
I'm FBI now.
You fucking came back.
Marshall says "hi-ya."
-Go fuck yourself. Mikey.
-Fuck you too. Danny.
-Eat a dick.
-Bitch.
I didn't realize everyone
missed me so much.
I would have come back sooner.
Yeah. well.
they don't like me now either.
Because of me?
-[camera clicking]
-DOA's name is Caleb Easton.
-Yeah. Jay Easton's son.
-[camera clicking]
[Danny] His dad's a billionaire.
So he's actually slumming it
in this house?
I know. it's a real shithole.
[Alice] Didn't wanna work
at his dad's hedge fund?
Dad made him a judge.
He left the bench.
Overdoses out of nowhere.
according to the sister.
Yeah. well. if there's one thing
everyone in the world
is honest about. it's doing drugs.
I learned that at Quantico.
-Did you get an A for that?
-Plus.
[Danny] You don't miss this?
Smell of a dead body in a hallway?
[inhales deeply]
Mm.
[Alice] Lacerations on his fingers.
Got lividity on the side of the arm.
Needle marks are too neat.
You know this isn't an O.D.
-It's staged.
-No kidding.
So. what?
You don't wanna be the one
to tell the lieutenant
you guys just caught another body?
I already told Marty.
I think his exact words were.
"You better fucking find a way
that we don't have to catch the guy
that killed Jay Easton's son."
So you dumped it on me?
We could do it together.
[Alice sniffing]
-Bleach.
-Hm.
Someone really wanted this room clean.
Nothing good
ever happens in the bathroom.
It's the one thing in this world
I know to be true.
He didn't see a lot of people.
He had a girlfriend. recent.
Um. sister hadn't met her yet.
didn't even know her name.
-A dealer?
-Could be a dealer.
We're looking at all
the security camera footage.
[breathing deeply]
You okay?
What are you doing?
I'm sitting on the floor for a second.
What's it look like?
[people laughing]
I'm sorry I brought you here.
I didn't think how it'd be coming back
and seeing the guys.
Hey.
Lacerations on his fingers?
Holy shit. I gotta call Marty.
-Go call Marty.
-Goddamn it!
[gasps lightly]
Let's see what we got.
Jinny. you alright to take
the breathalyzer tonight?
-[chuckles]
-Okay. no. Let's do this.
You take a walk around the block.
you come back.
-and I will save you your bed. okay?
-[chuckles]
It's gonna be alright. honey.
You just walk it off.
Hi. Vera.
Just go on in. alright?
Everybody else. we are full up.
Family Center might have some beds.
You were here yesterday. yeah?
You gotta get here earlier.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey. Jinny.
You want some?
Hit me and I'll give it to you.
[Jinny] Fuck off.
-Hit me!
-[scoffs]
Hit me!
Fucking hit me!
Fucking bitch!
-[grunting]
-Fuck off!
[shelter worker]
Jinny! Get off of her!
-[Jinny] Hey. that's my bag!
-[shelter worker] Hey!
-Hey. get back here!
-She took my bag.
[spitting]
[line ringing]
Hello?
Is this the. uh...
[operator]
Domestic Violence Hotline.
-Are you somewhere safe?
-No.
-Please help me. Please.
-Yes. we can help you.
-Help me.
-It's okay. It's okay.
I'm so scared.
-I am so scared.
-I understand.
I went back to him.
Let me send you the address
to the nearest shelter.
I'll just need to know
where you're located so I can find it.
Really?
Oh. thank you!
Thank you. thank you. thank you!
And do you have an ID?
Uh. I just ran out.
I didn't. um...
All I have is this bag I grabbed.
Oh. God. does that mean that I can't...
-No. no. It's... it's okay.
-Oh. my God. um...
-This happens.
-You know. I think that I. um...
I mean. I have...
-I have my SNAP card.
-Yeah. yeah. Yeah. that's good.
-That's good. yeah. has your name on it.
-Yeah?
It's good.
And if you stay here long enough.
we'll send a letter
to prove your residency. and then
we'll get you set up with a new I.D.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-[sighs]
This shelter is completely anonymous.
It's not listed anywhere.
No one's allowed to give out the address.
and there will be no record
of you being here.
So. it's okay.
You're safe now.
I'm Jinny.
-Welcome. Jinny.
-[sighs]
[laughter. chatter]
[♪ "Blue Disco"
by Arlo Parks playing]
♪ We're doin' dishes ♪
♪ The party's starting to thin ♪
♪ Aleda's cousin is out the back.
bein' sick ♪
♪ The walls are scratched up ♪
♪ It smells of chips and gin ♪
-Alice!
-Yes.
-Hi!
-Sorry I'm late.
I... Yes. I'm Alice.
I'm so glad you're here! Okay!
Uh. these are my bridesmaids.
-This is Kayla.
-Hi.
Shari. Lily. Natalie. and Kayla.
-Wait. you're both named Kayla?
-[laughter]
[sing-song]
And we love each other so much!
Oh. my God. I cannot believe
that you're actually here.
They didn't even believe
that I had a sister
because they haven't met you yet.
-Right.
-So it's kind of a special moment.
-So you're an FBI agent.
-Yes.
Do you have. like.
a gun on you right now?
Yes. Two.
There's a Glock on my hip
and a mini Glock on my leg.
And I could hurt everyone at this table.
[all laughing]
-That's so funny!
-Oh. my God!
Actually. I'm not going to be able
to stay very long at all
because I have a. a date.
A first date.
-Okay.
-Good for you!
Yeah. He seems really nice.
-Good for you. Good for you.
-That's really good.
-Cheers to nice.
-Nice is good.
-To nice guys!
-To nice!
To nice.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[exclaiming]
[growling]
[shouting]
[both shouting]
-[thuds]
-[groaning]
Whoa. I'm sorry.
Was that... was that too much?
No. but...
[exhales sharply]
I think I'm done.
You don't wanna fuck?
-Not tonight. I'm sorry.
-Oh. man.
Because like you said.
like on your profile.
that you wanted to fuck afterwards. so.
[Alice breathing heavily]
[vibrator buzzing]
-[phone ringing]
-[computer keys clacking]
Hey.
Do you remember Adrian Murado?
[Danny] Where are you?
You sound like you're in the woods
trying to start a fire.
[Alice] I'm not doing anything.
I'm eating snacks.
Adrian Murado was an overdose
that came through right before I left.
It was the same thing.
He had a girlfriend no one had met.
The scene was cleaned up afterwards.
-Just look it up.
-It's midnight.
What kind of snacks you eating?
Um. goldfish?
[printer whirring]
Forgot how much you love hard copies.
Hey. I like to hold shit in my hands.
Why did they move you over here?
You know how this place is.
After you left.
everyone was talking shit.
Lieutenant asked me why you missed
those couple days of work.
and I told him the truth.
That it was all Marshall's fault.
It's fine.
Just a fucking desk.
-You gonna eat that?
-Please don't eat my fucking sandwich.
You eat like an animal.
Swallow it. for the love of God.
Use a napkin.
-Is that the girlfriend?
-Yeah.
From a couple neighbors'
security cameras.
She's always hiding her face.
-[Alice] Anyone ever speak to her?
-[Danny] Yeah.
Here. look.
-[computer mouse clicking]
-That's the neighbor's kid.
-And...
-[computer mouse clicking]
that's her.
-We gotta talk to that kid.
-Obviously. I'm working on it.
She looks so small.
[Danny] Yeah. I told the lieutenant
it might be a woman.
He told me it's bullshit.
Told me now that I got divorced.
I must hate women.
Told me I need to get on the apps
and learn to fucking love again.
Of course you fucking hate women.
What's that got to do with anything?
Adrian Murado...
went to jail in 2012
for a drug charge.
He was dealing drugs
out of some bars downtown.
Looks like he found God in prison.
got sober.
and then stayed out of trouble
for a couple years.
And the neighbors
say they saw a woman?
A couple months before he died.
neighbors said they saw a woman
going in and out of the house.
Descriptions of her
are all over the place
'cause no one really ever met her.
But there's no pictures.
there's no video.
He shows up as an overdose
and no one thinks twice about him.
And look.
-Scratch marks.
-[Danny] Okay. come on.
-Come on.
-No. it can't be the same woman.
Why would she kill an ex-con.
and then a year later.
do the same thing
to Jay Easton's son?
How are those two guys connected?
They're not even on the same planet.
[♪ rhythmic dramatic music playing]
I give back to New York
because New York gave so much to me.
Which is why education
is going to be the central focus
of the Easton Family Endowment.
[Emma] [on video]
Let's put our hands together
for the recipients of the first-ever
Easton Family Endowment Scholarship
for Continuing Education.
Vivica and Tenise. please stand up.
[applause]
[video stops]
[elevator dings]
-Hi.
-[door closes]
Hey. Do you know
where Nora Washington is?
She's reviewing CSAM in there.
-I can wait.
-She's reviewing child pornography.
I would maybe pick
a different time to come down.
-It's fine.
-Okay.
We have cheese balls.
-I-If you're hungry.
-No.
[crunches]
-Hi. I was wondering if...
-Whatever it is. put it in an email.
[assistant crunching]
Actually. I... I don't want
to put it in an email.
because this could be relevant
to an ongoing homicide investigation.
Oh.
You're the ex-cop.
-I heard you requested my squad.
-[bags rustling]
Why do you want to work down here?
Why do you want to work in the basement
on sex crimes
and crimes against children?
Do you hate yourself?
Don't answer that.
I got an idea.
Why don't you go to white collar crimes.
meet your future husband?
I'm not here looking for a husband.
I just need information
about Adrian Murado.
I found your 302 from 2010.
You suspected him of trafficking girls.
I think it's possible
that one of the girls he trafficked
might have killed him.
Adrian Murado died of an overdose
about a year ago.
but the details of his death
are similar to the recent homicide
of Caleb Easton.
Both victims have a girlfriend
who no one had met.
and both times.
the girlfriend disappeared.
So. you think it's the girlfriend.
and you think she's a serial killer.
Oh. You're fucked.
You're not gonna make it
out of your probationary period.
We are FBI agents.
We're not homicide detectives.
Thanks for stopping by.
You've worked
on 273 homicide cases
related to trafficking
since you started.
You had one last week.
A girl was beaten to death
with a pipe to her face.
You wanna go for a ride?
Grab a box.
I thought the baby would change him.
I mean. I thought that he would change.
Surprise...
[sobbing]
I can't do this.
That's okay.
[sniffling] And I... I can't do it.
-It's just...
-Hey.
You can just pretend he's not real.
M-My boyfriend?
Yeah.
You can just pretend
none of it really happened.
Is there any way you could help me
get an ID so I can look for work?
Yeah. Yeah. uh...
-How long would that take?
-Oh. uh...
Um. did you say something
about a letter you could write?
Yeah. uh...
but y-you do have to stay here
for 60 days first
-before I can...
-Oh.
But. uh...
you know. if you tell me
you're planning on staying that long.
I can fudge some stuff.
if you want.
Okay.
I mean. I don't wanna get you
in any trouble.
You saved my life.
Do you have a laptop?
Is there any way I could borrow it?
[Alice] So. she's always late?
[Nora] Yeah.
And I'm always on time.
You want to be in this squad?
This is what it is.
-So what do you want to know?
-I know Murado was dealing drugs.
but you questioned him
about trafficking girls.
Why didn't the case go forward?
Do you know how hard it is
to get a trafficking case to stick?
Our legal system wants everything
put in chronological order.
They want a story that makes sense.
But these girls have no idea
about dates and times and places.
They've been locked in a hotel room.
or massage parlor.
Their IDs have been taken.
and they're usually high.
They're in love with the man
that did this to them.
which is worse than being high.
And once you take money for sex
in this country.
even if you're just a teenager.
you're a criminal.
You're less than human.
you're a piece of garbage.
So. these girls don't want to talk to me.
They don't trust me.
And they have no housing
and no way to make an income.
So. guess what?
They go right back to the traffickers.
-And that's what happened with Murado?
-I don't know.
-It was 16 years ago.
-You don't remember?
The girl that was beaten to death
last week.
if I play my cards right.
I'm not gonna remember her at all.
[radio volume increasing]
[Nora singing along]
♪ All my life ♪
♪ I prayed for someone like you ♪
Do you remember if any of...
♪ I thank God ♪
♪ That I. that I finally found you ♪
♪ All my life ♪
Adrian Murado is dead.
He was a bad man.
Maybe he overdosed.
maybe he was murdered.
Does it matter?
Yeah. it does.
It's our duty to get...
[knocking]
-Who is this?
-Hi.
I'm Alice Black.
I'm an FBI agent.
Hey. Tina. have you eaten today?
Come on.
come get snacks in the trunk.
I'm coming tomorrow at 3 p.m.
to pick you up and take you into court.
Fuck that.
I... I'm not going.
I told you. I... I thought I saw him.
You are going. and this is what
you're going to wear.
[scoffs]
I'm not wearing this shit.
Fine. I'll go in there
and tell 'em you're a minor.
That's fucked up.
You want me to lose my job?
[Alice] You want this?
Try it.
Come here.
FBI. put your hands up!
Yeah. I said. FBI!
Put your fucking hands up!
[sputtering]
-I got you.
-That got me.
♪
[♪ tense music playing]
[Alice] We're here to talk about
your neighbor. Caleb Easton.
There's a woman in this video...
My son barely spoke to this woman
and she's wearing a hospital mask.
I don't know why
we have to talk to the police.
Actually. I'm from the FBI.
I... I didn't do anything. Dad.
Don't worry.
Let's just talk.
So. I know you were smoking pot
on your stoop.
-No. I wasn't...
-We aren't going to talk about that.
My dad was a cop. you wouldn't even
believe the places I hid smoking pot.
So. you were sitting out
on your stoop.
and you saw a woman
walk into your neighbor's house
in the middle of the night.
You said you didn't see her face.
but really anything you can tell us
would help.
Anything you remember?
Yeah. well.
I didn't want to say this earlier.
but she flashed me.
I was just sitting on my stoop.
and she walked around
and fully lifted up her skirt
and showed me her vulva.
-Her what?
-It's actually the correct terminology.
The. uh. the outside is the vulva.
whereas the inside is the vagina.
I'm texting your dad.
I don't think that this is...
I have two dads.
Is there anything
you can remember about her?
Uh. well. I didn't really see her face.
so I-I didn't notice
what she looked like.
'cause I was mainly looking
at her vulva.
That makes sense.
She did have a tattoo though.
It was like a... a little red flower.
-Can you draw it?
-Uh. yeah.
[Alice] Is that a poppy?
I don't know shit about flowers.
Why'd you tell him
your dad was a cop?
He needed to feel
like we were on the same side.
FBI made you a better liar.
[chuckles softly]
Always been a good liar.
[people chattering]
Where you been?
I'm actually still helping out the P.D.
on the Caleb Easton homicide.
Oh. yeah. no. don't worry about that.
I. uh. I spoke to leadership.
and we feel your time's better spent
in the call center.
We're not gonna pursue Caleb Easton.
Oh. who did you speak to?
What does it matter?
Stay in your lane.
Do what the bureau needs you to do.
[shelter worker] [over PA]
Last call for dinner.
If anyone is still
in the sleeping area.
last call for dinner
in the cafeteria.
What are you doing here?
-Why do you have that?
-I had to confiscate
the drugs that were in the bag.
It's a drug-free facility.
[bag thuds]
Also. um...
sorry. and... and I have to ask.
who's Oliver Charles?
[muttering indistinctly]
On my computer looking up some guy.
kind of a lot.
Fancy rich lawyer guy
you're trying to bag? [chuckles]
Just wondering.
-You're jealous.
-No.
[chuckles softly]
I'm just trying to look out
for your mental health.
It's my job.
Guess you might need this.
Uh...
The showers are. uh.
they're warm again...
-Mm.
-today.
I hope you're not mad at me.
No. I. uh...
You are so beautiful.
You think so?
I... I have a girlfriend.
[whispering] That's nice.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[♪ "Wonderful Illusion"
by Eartha Kitt playing]
Pen. W4.
Okay.
Jinny. do you have any issues
with raw beef?
-No. I love it.
-[chuckles]
♪ What is this wonderful illusion ♪
♪ This ever-burning flame ♪
♪ That fills me
with a strange confusion ♪
♪ Each time I hear your name ♪
Oh. what's this?
I forgot what it's called.
Hm.
Well. I'll take one anyway.
I'm Jinny.
I'm Oliver.
♪ I'm yours alone ♪
[phone buzzing]
Hello. who is this?
Yeah. this is her.
[Nora] Who called you?
Uh. the blazer I gave her.
my card was in the pocket.
How is she?
She's not breathing on her own.
I didn't realize she was 15.
She was a trafficker.
Every new girl she brought in
meant she had to work less herself.
That's how I got her to talk.
I told her we'd prosecute her.
What's that smell?
Tequila.
I'm drunk.
♪
[Oliver]
I got this place after the divorce.
[sniffing]
[snorting]
[sighs]
I was married to my wife for 14 years.
and then I was just like.
I gotta get out.
'cause she was just
talking and talking.
I mean. I literally thought if I hear
one more word out of her fucking mouth.
I'm gonna expire.
Like. listening to her talk
was gonna actually fucking kill me.
And you know. yeah.
I had a sex addiction.
but. I mean. she knew that going in.
She acted like I was a monster.
[sniffling]
Where are you from?
-Guess.
-I don't know.
Um. Ohio or something.
How did you know?
You're so real.
[chuckles softly]
What do... what do you want to do?
Uh. I want to be a nurse. I think.
My wife never had to work for anything.
I had to work. so I did.
You know. I put in the hours.
I think I'm building something. you know.
but then I'm just. like.
part of this machine.
And I just... it's like.
I want to feel alive again.
Hang on.
[sniffing]
[♪ soft music playing]
-So. I le... I left her.
-Mm-hmm.
And. um. I started doing
more pro bono work.
Uh. I do a lot of
international education stuff with girls.
-Mm!
-That's helped me sort of feel
like a human being again.
'Cause that...
a big thing is I haven't...
It's like I... I can't feel
anything anymore.
[whispering] I feel everything.
I wanna touch you and fuck you.
Is that okay?
Is that okay to say?
[whispering] Yeah.
Um. give me... I'll be...
give me one second.
I'm just... I'm gonna get an NDA.
[drawer opens. closes]
[♪ soft music continues playing]
Here you go. um.
take a look. I guess. and...
Honestly. they're a good thing.
You'll be glad that we have it. too.
[♪ soft music stops playing]
[♪ "Don't Let Me Be Misunderstood"
by Elvis Costello begins playing]
[singing along] ♪ Baby. can you
understand me now ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel a little mad ♪
What does this say?
To... uh. that you consent
to having sex with me.
-You do. right?
-Yeah. [chuckles]
Thank you.
[singing] ♪ I'm just a soul
whose intentions are good ♪
♪ Oh. Lord. please don't let me
be misunderstood ♪
-[chuckles]
-[whispering] This part.
♪
[Nora] Here.
This is what I had on Adrian Murado.
Female serial killers. for the most part.
know their victims.
They usually kill
for power. control. money.
It's evolution.
-Are you nervous?
-How did you know?
I feel like I just get you.
I can't get naked...
while you're watching.
[whispering]
Could you close your eyes?
Okay.
-Your room is so big.
-Mm.
[Nora] Obviously. any woman
who becomes a serial killer
is the victim of something but
lots of women have terrible lives.
and not all of them start to kill.
So. why does someone
start to murder people?
Hey. where'd you go?
-Jinny?
-I'm here.
I want you...
-so bad.
-[moaning]
Fuck! Hey.
Don't do that again.
I'm sorry.
I'm really nervous.
You know the story of Medusa?
With snakes in her hair?
Her hair is snakes.
She's so ugly.
she kills men with one look.
-[sighs]
-And you know how she got that way?
She got raped by Poseidon.
How do you know that?
Because I'm not a former cop.
I went to a fancy school.
and I'm very smart.
Okay. fuck you.
The god of the ocean
rapes her in Athena's temple.
but Athena decides
that's Medusa's fault.
and turns all her beautiful golden hair
into snakes.
[Oliver moans softly]
She's a victim.
But it doesn't make her a good person.
[gasps]
Sorry.
[Nora]
It turns her into a monster.
[whispering] No.
I liked it.
Do it again.
Do anything you want to me.
♪
[Nora] Juries want to believe
that women who are victims of
violence are all good people
but in my experience.
being a victim of violence
just makes you colder.
more calculating.
Victims of violence
are the most violent.
Don't you think so?
I looked you up.
You were in this hospital a year ago.
Your cop boyfriend
knock you around a little?
Is that why you left the police?
Needed to heal your pain?
Yikes.
Sorry. Too soon.
Yeah. well. we all have something.
That's what I'm saying.
that's the world that makes sense.
Women are supposed
to be hit and raped.
and go away and die quietly.
not start murdering people.
Everyone likes it
when there's a sweet little woman
lying on the floor naked
and cut up in pieces.
I get so fucking angry.
[sighs]
It doesn't matter.
Anything you do.
the ones who are really to blame
don't get caught. Never.
Never.
You think you're ever gonna
catch anyone who matters?
♪
[♪ eerie music playing]
[whispering]
Georgie Porgie. pudding and pie.
Kissed the girls and made them cry.
[indistinct audio on video]
When the boys came out to play...
[girl screaming on video]
Georgie Porgie ran away.
[screaming continues]
[♪ eerie music playing]
[whispering] Got you.
[♪ "Wonderful Illusion"
by Eartha Kitt playing]
♪ What is this wonderful illusion ♪
♪ This ever-burning flame ♪
♪ That fills me with
a strange confusion ♪
♪ Each time I hear your name ♪
♪ There is something in your eyes
and in your sighs ♪
♪ That speaks of heaven ♪
♪ In the warmth of your caress
I must confess ♪
♪ I'm yours alone ♪
♪ This sweet and wonderful illusion ♪
♪ I've never known before ♪
♪ It was born the night we met ♪
♪ I can't forget ♪
♪ That magic moment... ♪